Oh! It's coming! It's coming!
Why?
Because people are rattling around, you'd think it's springing up.
No, it is.
Open!
Ta-da!
Hello, everyone.
Good evening.
Well...
As you can see.
I, too, was struck by fear.
God help me.
And yet...
I'm...
I'm saying this all by myself.
I think it's a little crazy
I think it is.
Last time we had meat steaks and sausages
I was able to do it!
And now, the end of the day!
Ta-da!
Let's make komoto!
I love comoto!
So I would like to make komoto!
Fill a large pot with about 1400 ml of water.
When water comes to a boil, add sugar and simmer for about 12 minutes until noodles are tender.
Once it comes to a boil, add the miso paste, bring to a boil one more time, and you are done.
Okay, so first, in this large pot,
1400 ml
You see, I don't have it on me.
It's not on the pan.
So I'm going to use my intuition.
I'll fill it up.
Have a good day.
Where, where, where, where, where, where?
A thousand miles
It's like this
I bet it's just like this
it tastes so rich, but it's okay
I'm going to bring this to a boil
I think I'll add a little wood
Yoo-hoo!
I'm gonna add wood.
All right.
Watch this.
I can do this.
Here you go.
Here we go.
Finally, it's done.
That's good.
Good.
Yes, I'm serious.
Here we go.
Welcome.
What are you drinking?
Oh! Oh, no! How to cook!
What am I drinking?
Quiz!
(1) Cocoa
Milk tea
Corn soup
Swinking time has started!
I can't stop thinking about it.
What is it?
Yay!
There are so many fish!
They're flying around!
Just like the old me.
I'm wearing one of these right now, and I'm looking for the other one.
You're such an idiot.
That's right.
It's so hot!
I need to sleep.
Not yet... not yet...
Not yet, not yet, not yet.
Oh, yeah, the answer to this.
You back there?
Oh, Coke is so good.
It's like milk tea.
Milk tea? Tea au lait?
I'm gonna get shaggy.
It's warm.
Can't wait for it to boil.
Me and my cousin, we're both graduating high school, and we're old enough to go to college or vocational school.
My family, my cousin, my grandma and I went to Chinatown to eat some really good koji food.
I told her that I bought some souvenirs for them.
I said, "What did you buy? I said, "What did you buy?
I said, "Rice crackers with a cute, wide character?
I said, "I bought some rice crackers with a cute, wide character or something, like a printed rice cracker with a bird character and a boat on it.
Okay, that's cute.
I thought I got you something a little more robust.
Cute like that.
I don't know.
It makes my heart proud.
He's cute.
Yes, I am.
At that time, we were celebrating their graduation and their future endeavors.
I had prepared cosmetics and other gifts for the two of them.
I rushed out to buy them in the fall time.I rushed out to buy some stuff in the fall time.
I bought the recommended DeForte primer, Jellicheat blush, and a bunch of other stuff.
I left them with my mom and asked her to follow me and give them to me.
She seemed to be really happy with it.
My guy doesn't seem to have much experience with makeup.
So I gave him something easy to use.
He seemed really happy.
I hadn't exchanged contact information with him, but he wanted to.
But he thought that he shouldn't connect with me.
But my sister told me about it, and I told her on LINE that I was really happy.
I'm really happy when people thank me.
I'm sorry. Please tell me soon. I'm so excited.
It's not coming. It's not coming.
Just when I think it's about to happen, it starts to happen.
That's funny.
That's why I lowered the height.
Lower it.
It looks more like it's about to come up.
More bumps.
Air... air... bumps...
There's more of it.
It feels like it's coming up.
I have a feeling it's coming.
Oh, it's coming, it's coming, it's coming, it's coming.
Maybe. I don't know.
I'm so backward and forgetful.
There's a lot of people fishing.
Oh my God, it's like a dragonfly!
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Don't come this way, please.
I've been here before, but it's okay to say that they've already sprung up, right?
I'm sure it's fine.
It's fine. It's fine.
Please, please, please.
No, it's boiling.
Maybe we'll just say it's boiling.
All right, then.
One thing I can't wait to do.
I'm going to put in the noodles.
Noodles
Throttle tone
No, it's boiling.
It's boiling like crazy.
It looks like it's going to fly
Here we go.
Throw in the noodles!
Go, go, go, go, go!
Loosen, loosen, loosen.
Until they're soft.
What's this?
Keep loosening the noodles.
Put it in.
Until your hands are soft.
Okay, ladies and gentlemen, you have 12 minutes from here.
Okay.
See you all in 12 minutes.
I'll see you all in 12 minutes.
Oh!
You.
Ladies and gentlemen...
It hasn't been 12 minutes yet.
It's boiling over, and it's a big mess.
I'm going to put the vegetables in for now.
Vegetables and meat.
The pumpkin we had this time.
It was like a Houtou style.
I wonder what this pumpkin is?
Kabocha, potatoes, carrots and burdock root!
Thank goodness!
And thank goodness it's soft!
The wind
It's amazing!
I like Kosaku's houtou the best.
I've had it at a lot of different houtou restaurants, and I love it.
I want to try that one at Kosaku, Suiton.
Suiton Suiton
Oh, here comes Tombi.
I want to try Suiton.
Have you ever had it?
Oh, my gosh.
That's great. I put too much in at once.
Oh, my God.
Here.
I'll stare at it.
Oh, my God.
Looks so good.
Stare, stare, stare.
Wow, looks delicious
Nice I want to eat it
Look at me over here.
I bought these clothes too.
Colombia.
It's onagi!
Colombia is so cute!
Now I'd like to put out some more water.
Here it comes!
It's getting cold.
But it's coming to a boil, so that's good.
I'm going to put miso in here.
Have a good day!have a good day
Miso, miso, miso.
Mix it up.
Mix, mix, mix.
Looks good.
No birds.
Looks so good!
And then it's done.
And a little bit more.
A little more lip color.
A little bit.
Good night.
Smells good!
I think I got something.
Good, good, good, good, good.
Is it done?
It's done! It's done!
I'll show you now.
Wait a minute.
It's open!
Wow!
Looks delicious!
It's ready!
Bon appétit!
Wow, it looks delicious!
Sizzling!
Put the white topping
Put the white topping on top!
Thank you for watching!
Bon appétit!
Don't be cold.
Eat fries.
There's warmth piling up in here.
It's warm in here.
Don't be cold.
Eat fries
There's warmth piling up in here.
Yum!
Happy!
I wish everyone could taste this joy and happiness.
I hope you will have it in your hands as well.
See you soon!
That's all for today's video.
Near the end
Let's eat!
See you soon!
Eat moist but
Well, bye-bye!
It was delicious!
Please subscribe to our channel!